loopster.com 2019-05-26

# Privacy Policy

Loopster, Inc. ("Loopster," "we," "our" or "us") is committed to respecting the privacy and security of your personal information. The following U.S. online privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes the information we collect and how we use it. By using this website, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

We may periodically update this Privacy Policy to reflect material changes in how we collect, use, share or store your personal information. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current Privacy Policy. You consent to any changes we make to this Privacy Policy if you continue to use the Loopster service after receiving a notice of the change or upon our posting of the new Privacy Policy on this website.

## COLLECTING INFORMATION

Like many websites, we gather information about how visitors use our website. In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track your visit for trends and statistics, but you will remain anonymous unless you tell us who you are. Once you choose to give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. For more information, see the "Navigation" section of this Privacy Policy below.

We request information from you (which may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, gender and, when necessary, credit card information) when you:

  * Register or set up an account
  * Purchase a subscription
  * Request to receive communications
  * Participate in a promotion or other website feature
  * Participate in online discussions
  * Modify your account or profile

In order to better understand your preferences and better serve you, we may combine information you give us online with other information from Loopster sources, transactions and communications. This may include data from Loopster direct mail, events, or online marketing. We may also combine that information with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources. This data may include postal address updates and demographic data. All data combined and stored with online data is protected by this Privacy Policy.

To provide you with certain social features, we may collect information about you, your contacts, or friends from third party websites that provide access to this information, such as Facebook, YouTube, LinkedIn, Twitter, or email services. We respect and follow the privacy policies of those third party services with regard to the data we collect from them.

To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will never knowingly or intentionally collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, we will immediately delete that information. Because we do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13, to the best of our knowledge and belief, we have no such information to use or to disclose to a third party.

The information we collect in this survey provides Loopster with information regarding the personal preferences, interests, profile and demographics of our user community. We use this information to, among other things, improve our service, communicate with you regarding promotions, special offers, and both ours and third party offerings that may be of interest to you. if you are not interested in participating, please feel free to skip the survey. Additional information regarding our collection and use of information, and the process to “opt-out” can be located in our privacy policy located on our website.

To make a payment to Loopster, we require you to provide your billing details, such as a name, address, email address and financial information corresponding method of payment (e.g. a credit card number and expiration date or a bank account number). If you provide a billing address, we will regard that as the location of the account holder.

## USING INFORMATION

We may use the information we collect to:

  * Customize and/or personalize your communications and user experience
  * Better respond to your customer service inquiries
  * Communicate with you about your purchase, account information, or customer service needs
  * Communicate with you about our products/services, events, and for other promotional purposes
  * Display targeted advertising, announcements, sponsorships or other messages
  * Improve our business
  * Administer competitions, contests, promotions, surveys or other website features

We will not use your personal information to advertise or communicate promotional offers, directly or indirectly, using direct mail marketing or telemarketing, unless you give us permission to do so.

We may extend any of our rights under this Privacy Policy to third parties performing services on our behalf.

We use your billing details to process subscription and service charges to your account. We also occasionally send you communications of a transactional nature, e.g. billing-related matters.

## SHARING INFORMATION

We may enable other users of our site and third parties to view or receive information from your profile, subject to your permission to share this information. These third-parties may include social networking providers such as Facebook, Linked-In, Twitter, MySpace and YouTube, as well as individual subscribers to these third-party services. With your permission, we may publish or distribute selected information about you, such as your recommendations, interests and other data or content of possible interest to other users of our site and third parties.

For the purpose of operating our business, we may transfer information between Loopster and our preferred service providers who use that information only to conduct Loopster business. For example, they may handle our credit card processing, shipping, data management, email distribution, market research, information analysis, and promotions management. We provide our preferred service providers with the information they need to perform their services and work with them to respect and protect your information.

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with carefully selected persons or companies whom we believe trustworthy. In such cases we might share and cross-reference information, including personally identifiable information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share any information with these companies, please email Loopster at [support@loopster.com](mailto:support@loopster.com) to update your privacy settings.

We may provide your information to our wholly-owned companies and affiliates, which may be outside the United States. We may also sell or transfer your personal information to third parties in connection with any merger, acquisition, reorganization, change in capital structure or sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Loopster.

We may provide information to other companies for purposes such as reporting and marketing. We may sell or transfer non-individualized information to third parties, including summary or aggregated anonymous information about all or sub-groups of users of our site.

On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

Mostly commonly, we share your information with our service providers who help us to provide our services to you. We contractually bind these service providers to keep your information confidential and to use it only for the purpose of providing their services to us. For example, we use payment processors who help us to process credit card transactions. By using our services, you authorize Loopster to sub-contract in this manner on your behalf. 

If your details (as the account holder) are different to the billing contact listed for your account, we may disclose your identity and account details to the billing contact upon their request (we also will usually attempt to notify you of such requests). By using our services and agreeing to this privacy policy, you consent to this disclosure.

## PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

We use a variety of security measures, including sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secure networks and is only accessible to a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be accessed only as stated above. We will use the information for purposes of processing and completing only those transactions you approve, and the information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete a specific transaction. Regardless of these efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Our site may contain hypertext links to the websites of one or more third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites.

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who may place advertisements on our site may use their own cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, web bugs and other technology to collect information about you. We do not control these companies' use of such technology and we have no responsibility for the use of such technology by these companies to gather information about you.

## NAVIGATION

Like other interactive websites, we collect information about your use of our site and our services using cookies, log files, and techniques used to track who is reading a web page or e- mail, when, and from what computer, such as web bugs, web beacons or pixel tags.

A cookie is a small removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer.

Cookies allow you to order a subscription to our products and services on our website and allow us to enhance and personalize your online browsing and shopping experience.

For example, we use cookies to:

  * Recognize you when you return to our website
  * Analyze visitor behavior
  * Store session data

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (i.e. Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookie settings.

Pixel tags, also known as web beacons or web bugs, are tiny graphic images (referred to here as "GI") that are unobtrusively placed on a website or in an e-mail. When the HTML code for the GI points to a site to retrieve the image, it simultaneously passes information to our servers, such as the IP address of the computer that retrieved the image, the time and duration the GI was viewed, the type of browser that retrieved the image, and previously set cookie values.

We use GI to help us analyze your online behavior. We may use GI to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with our sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring web site addresses. We also use GI to allow us to send you email in a format you can read and to let us know when you have opened an email message from us.

We also work with other companies who use tracking technologies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our communications, including advertising. If you would like to opt-out of allowing third party companies to collect non-personally identifiable information about you during your visits to our site, please email Loopster at [support@loopster.com](mailto:support@loopster.com) to update your privacy settings.

## HOW TO REVIEW, MODIFY OR DELETE YOUR INFORMATION

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us or would like to update or change your personal information or preferences, follow the instructions below to review, modify or delete your personal information.

To modify the information you have provided during registration, please login and update your personal settings.

To unsubscribe from an email, please follow the instructions in any email you receive.

If you request your registration information be deleted or if you unsubscribe from communications, we may maintain information about sales transactions or service inquiries for future service and record keeping purposes.

## QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please contact us by mail or email at:

Loopster, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
P.O. Box 1536  
Grand Junction, CO. 81502  

## COMPLAINTS

If you have a data privacy complaint, please contact us by mail or email at:

Loopster, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
P.O. Box 1536  
Grand Junction, CO. 81502  

## TERMS OF USE

Please also visit our Terms of Use that explain other terms governing the use of our site.
